secure-res.com 2019-01-29

# Privacy Policy

At Vizergy, we understand that privacy is important to you. We are providing this Privacy Statement to help you understand how we may collect and use information.

## General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 

Vizergy has measures in place which meet the principles of data protection by design and data protection by default (per GDPR Article 25). Additionally, we have verified that our vendors and partners are in compliance with the GDPR or plan to be in compliance before May 25, 2018. If you have a GDPR question or concern or would like to receive a full copy of our GDPR addendum to this privacy policy, please email us at [privacy@vizergy.com](mailto:privacy@vizergy.com)

##  What does this privacy policy cover?

This privacy policy describes the privacy practices of Vizergy’s websites. Note that “websites” include web-based services such as the Vizergy Marketing System (VMS) and the SECURE-RES.COM reservation system. This privacy policy also applies to Vizergy’s marketing and advertising practices.

## What information does Vizergy collect about me? 

**Vizergy user account, registration, and customer support**

When you register to use a Vizergy website, create a Vizergy user account, or contact us for support or other offerings, Vizergy collects information that identifies you. This includes information such as your name, company name, email address, or payment information. We may also sometimes collect other information that does not identify you, such as which types of websites you’re interested in. Some of this information is required and other information is optional. To help keep our databases current and to provide you the most relevant content and experiences, we may combine information provided by you with information from other sources, in accordance with applicable law. For example, from these sources, we may learn about the size, industry, and other information about the company you work for.

## Vizergy websites

We collect information about how you use our websites. We may collect information sent by your browser or device to our servers whenever you visit a Vizergy website. For example, your browser or device may tell us your IP address (which may tell us generally where you are located) and the type of browser and device you used. When you visit a Vizergy website, your browser may also tell us information such as the page that led you to our website and, if applicable, the search terms you typed into a search engine that led you to our website. Vizergy may collect information about how you use our websites by using cookies and similar technologies, and our servers may collect similar information when you are logged in to the website. Depending on the website, this information may be anonymous or it may be associated with you.

Also, we use automated systems to analyze your content using techniques such as machine learning in order to improve our apps and websites. This analysis may occur as the content is sent or received using an online feature of a Vizergy website, or when the content is stored on Vizergy servers.

## Vizergy emails 

Emails we send you may include a technology (called a web beacon) that tells Vizergy whether you have received or opened the email or clicked a link in the email. If you do not want us to collect this information from Vizergy marketing emails, you can opt out of receiving Vizergy marketing emails.

## Vizergy online advertising 

Vizergy advertises online in a variety of ways, including displaying Vizergy ads to you on other companies' websites and apps. We collect information such as which ads are displayed, which ads are clicked on, and on where the ad was displayed.

## Buttons, tools, and content from other companies

Vizergy websites may include buttons, tools, or content that link to other companies’ services (for example, a Facebook "Like" button). We may collect information about your use of these features. In addition, when you see or interact with these buttons, tools, or content, or view a Vizergy web page or app containing them, some information from your browser may automatically be sent to the other company. Please read that company’s privacy policy for more information.

## Vizergy social networking pages and social sign-on services

Vizergy has its own pages on many social networking sites (for example, the Vizergy Facebook page). We may collect information when you interact with our social networking pages.

## SECURE-RES.COM Reservation System

SECURE-RES.COM auto sends an email to you upon the successful completion of the online reservation process.

· This email contains a reservation reference number generated by SECURE-RES.COM and details of the reservation. It also may contain customized information from the property you selected. That property is responsible for the contents of the customized portion of the automated email.

· If the property you selected subscribes to our automated Guest Welcome and Thank You Email Service, you may receive up to two additional emails. The property is responsible for the content of those emails.

· SECURE-RES.COM does not contact you via email except in the instances stated above or if you contact us about support.

## How does Vizergy use the information it collects about me?

Vizergy uses the information we collect about you in several ways, such as:

·      Providing you with the Vizergy websites for which you have registered, as well as any services, support, or information you have requested

·      Better understanding how our websites are being used so we can improve them and engage and retain users

·      Diagnosing problems in our websites

·      Tailoring a website or Vizergy ad to your likely interests

·      Sending you business messages such as those related to payments or expiration of your service

·      Sending you information about Vizergy, special offers, and similar information

·      Conducting market research about our customers, their interests, and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns

·      Reducing fraud and protecting you as well as Vizergy

## What are cookies and how does Vizergy use them? 

Vizergy uses cookies and similar technologies to make our websites work as well as to learn more about our users and their likely interests.

Vizergy websites may also use cookies and similar technologies from other companies that allow us to gather additional information to measure and improve the effectiveness of the Vizergy services. 

## Does Vizergy share my personal information?

Vizergy works with companies that help us run our business. These companies provide services such as delivering customer support, processing credit card payments, and sending emails on our behalf. In some cases, these companies have access to some of your personal information in order to provide services to you on our behalf. They are not permitted to use your information for their own purposes.

Vizergy may also share your personal information:

·      When you agreed to the sharing

·      With our resellers and other sales partners if you are a business customer and agreed to receive Vizergy marketing communications. Note that we do not share personal information about consumers with third parties for their own marketing purposes unless the consumer agreed to that sharing.

·      When we are required to provide information in response to a subpoena, court order, or other applicable law or legal process

·      When we have a good faith belief that the disclosure is necessary to prevent or respond to fraud, defend our websites against attacks, or protect the property and safety of Vizergy, our customers and users, or the public

·      If we merge with or are acquired by another company, sell a Vizergy website or business unit, or if all or a substantial portion of our assets are acquired by another company. In those cases your information will likely be one of the assets that is transferred

We may share or publish aggregate information that doesn’t specifically identify you, such as statistical information about visitors to our websites or statistical information about how customers use Vizergy services.

## Is my personal information secure?

We understand that the security of your personal information is important. We provide reasonable administrative, technical, and physical security controls to protect your personal information. However, despite our efforts, no security controls are 100% effective and Vizergy cannot ensure or warrant the security of your personal information.

## Where does Vizergy store my personal information?

Your personal information and files are stored on Vizergy’s servers and the servers of companies we hire to provide services to us. 

## How can I review or update my personal information or close my Vizergy user account?

Under the law of some countries, you may have the right to access the information Vizergy holds about you, correct mistakes in that information, and to delete personal information that we no longer have business reasons for retaining. The Vizergy Marketing System allows you to edit your personal information by accessing the "my account," "my profile," or a similar feature of the website you are using. Likewise, you can delete information you have stored in our websites by logging in and using the deletion functions they make available.

If you are a Vizergy client you can request that we remove your email address from our marketing database, deactivate your Vizergy user account, or provide you a copy of your personal information, please email your request to [privacy@vizergy.com](mailto:privacy@vizergy.com). Please note that we need to retain certain information about you for legal and internal business reasons, such as fraud prevention. We will retain your personal information for as long as necessary to provide you with the websites and apps you are eligible to use with your Vizergy user account and as needed to comply with our legal obligations and enforce our agreements.

If you are a visitor of a Vizergy client website then please contact the property directly for a personal information request.

## Will Vizergy market to me?

Vizergy and companies we hire to help us market our websites on our behalf may use your information to provide you with information and offers related to Vizergy. We give you choices regarding our marketing practices.

## What information is collected by companies using Vizergy services?

Vizergy solutions help our business customers personalize and improve the performance of their websites and marketing messages. For example, these customers may use the Vizergy Marketing System (VMS) to collect and analyze information about how you use their websites. The data collected is stored on our servers for use by these business customers.

## Will this privacy policy change?

Occasionally, we may change this privacy policy to allow Vizergy to use or share your personal information in a different way. We encourage you to periodically review the Vizergy Privacy Policy for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## Who can I contact with questions or concerns?

If you have a privacy question or concern, please email us at [privacy@vizergy.com](mailto:privacy@vizergy.com)
